[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 3]
¥800,000. Going once to Bidder No. 303.
As long as you're safe.
¥1,000,000. Going once to Bidder No. 250.
People are actually fighting over such an unknown thing.
I think
these two people
must have some personal grudge.
Exactly.
Boss.
Boss, please be rational.
Bidder No. 303, ¥2,000,000.
I…
Bidder No. 250, ¥2,500,000.
Bidder No. 303, ¥3,000,000.
Bidder No. 250, ¥3,500,000.
Bidder No. 303, ¥4,000,000.
Bidder No. 250, ¥4,500,000.
¥5,000,000.
Sorry, sir.
This painting is priceless to me.
But if you really like it,
you can come to my place and admire it anytime.
Let's just call it making friends.
¥8,000,000.
Sir,
I'm sorry.
You might not know me very well.
Anything I love,
I don't like to leave it at someone else's place to admire.
And I especially don't like it being admired by others.
Okay.
I'm really sorry, everyone.
Due to special circumstances,
the collector has suspended the auction.
The auction for this item
ends here.
That's not how it's done.
Apologies again.
How unruly.
The hammer falls, the deal is done.
That's the rule of the auction house.
What do you mean?
I'm really sorry, sir.
We are also communicating with the collector.
If there's any further news,
we will notify you immediately.
Sorry.
Ning Changyue.
You were the one who brought Yu Tu back,
but now you don't even care.
She's getting mud all over the house.
Lift your feet.
All you do is watch short dramas all day.
I wonder when you'll remember
how to break the vow to live forever together.
Move your big butt!
Since you are the only one, of course I cherish you.
Unlike others,
you are now…
-Give it to me! -No.
Give it to me!
No!
You are now a member of the Censorate,
working under the Crown Prince.
Osmanthus-themed Painting Special Exhibition.
Autumn Art Gallery.
I didn't expect anyone to be
as obsessed with that painting as I am.
I don't know why either.
The very first moment I saw that painting,
I just really liked it and wanted to own it.
Since you like it so much,
I want to get it even more.
Usually, when people hear someone really likes something,
shouldn't they instinctively
want to let the other person have it?
I'm a businessman.
I only care about value.
After I get it,
you'll buy it at any price,
won't you?
Nice to meet you.
Let's make friends.
My name is Lin Huai.
You went to this Autumn Art Gallery today?
What is an art gallery?
Ning Changyue.
He went out.
Went out?
Where did he go?
I don't know.
This is our first time meeting each other.
We're not close enough
to be considered friends.
Sorry, the number you've dialed is temporarily unavailable.
Aren't you going to wait for Ning Changyue to come back?
Are you going by yourself?
What if Ning Changyue makes some progress today?
Women
have to rely on themselves at critical moments.
Hello.
Of course.
It's an honor for us at Autumn Art Gallery.
Okay.
I'll go back now.
Autumn Art Gallery.
Why does it sound so familiar?
Sorry.
Our gallery is a private gallery
that collects works of niche anonymous painters.
It's not open to the public.
I'm sorry.
My apologies.
Help me check all the exhibitions about osmanthus trees.
Yes.
Paintings, calligraphy, vessels, and clothing patterns
with osmanthus tree elements.
Any kind.
I'll call you back later.
Did you draw this?
Yes. Thank you.
Your drawing is beautiful.
Many people think it's weird that I like drawing trees.
If you like it, it's yours.
There was love in your heart when you drew it.
Look.
All the branches
of this tree are desperately growing upward,
as if they could touch something
as long as they grow high enough.
It shows there's an obsession
in your heart.
Sorry, it's force of habit.
My name is Xie He,
a clinical psychologist
at Hexin Psychological Clinic.
[Xie He]
Song Yiqiu.
Nice to meet you.
Why is this guy here again in this life?
Song Yiqiu saved him again.
Autumn…
Lingering ghost.
Autumn Moon…
Autumn…
In this life,
I must never let him meet Song Yiqiu.
Autumn…
-Lingering ghost. -What do you mean?
Nothing.
Stop.
You…
Today,
where did you go?
Me?
To an auction.
An auction?
It was popular hundreds of years ago.
Why do you still want to go now?
Then what did you buy?
-I didn't… -Autumn…
I didn't buy anything.
I just looked around.
You dressed up so nicely.
Where did you go?
Don't mention it.
I got nothing.
"Autumn Moon in the Forest."
Did you find…
"Autumn Moon in the Forest"?
Song Yiqiu.
Deal with him.
"Autumn Moon in the Forest"
might be the sacred painting that seals time?
Such important news.
Why didn't you tell me?
Ning Changyue.
I'm talking to you.
Why didn't you take me with you?
It's not that I didn't want to take you with me.
I wasn't even sure myself
if this was reliable.
I think you're just feeling guilty.
What, was there someone I shouldn't see?
You knew it?
Was it your Miss Liu or Miss Wang?
But don't worry.
I know everything.
I don't care.
You don't have to hide it from me.
Yeah.
The auction. The antique shop. The top ten beauties were all there.
Of course I couldn't let you go.
And in the end, that painting went unsold.
The scroll was only half unrolled.
It would have been a waste of time if you went.
Could it be because you
have too much bad luck?
If it were me,
since I have better luck than you,
I definitely would have won the bid.
If you had gone,
someone else would have had the good luck.
What did you say?
I'm talking to you, Ning Changyue!
Alright, stop talking.
Let me think about it
and try to reconstruct it for you from memory.
We weren't allowed to take photos of the auction items.
I only took one look,
so I might not be able to reconstruct it perfectly.
Prepare the brush and ink.
Me?
Who else?
Didn't you want to see the painting?
You haven't seen it,
so you can only rely on me.
Alright.
Brush.
Ink.
Be serious.
This is delicate work.
Even a slight mistake will prevent you
from reproducing the elegance of "Autumn Moon in the Forest."
Are you going to draw or not?
Mountains.
A full moon.
What else?
Why did you stop drawing?
This tree crown…
I don't really know how to draw it.
Then do you still remember
what this tree crown looks like?
It has quite thick foliage.
And the branches stretch out in all directions,
forming a huge umbrella shape.
Didn't I teach you during the Southern Qin period?
Focus.
You can't even draw such a simple tree crown?
This tree crown…
This tree crown
is very tree crown-like.
I'll go call Yu Tu over here.
She should know
about the tree, right?
What do you mean by "very tree crown-like"?
What are you thinking about, Song Yiqiu?
You two are no longer
the Song Yiqiu and Ning Changyue from 3,000 years ago.
Did you forget?
It's so late.
Who is it?
You're…
Is this Mr. Ning's house?
No.
I got the wrong place?
But he's a tenant,
and I'm the landlord.
Have some water.
Thank you.
I didn't expect someone as successful as Mr. Ning
to still be…
-Fifteen. Fifteen. Fifteen. -Fifteen. Fifteen. Twenty.
Sharing a place with others.
Save when you can, spend when you should.
Manager Qing Yuan, you came to see me so late.
Is something the matter?
I came here specifically to apologize.
Today, the owner canceled the auction halfway through,
so you couldn't win the bid on "Autumn Moon in the Forest."
I'm sorry.
Now, this painting is in the Autumn Art Gallery.
Please look.
Autumn Art Gallery?
Can we go?
I'm sorry.
Autumn Art Gallery is a private collection museum
that is only open to VIP members.
[Autumn Art Gallery]